<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: stationary | LUKENPR]]></title>
  <link href="http://lukenpr.com/blog/categories/stationary/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://lukenpr.com/"/>
  <updated>2015-09-16T18:27:31+10:00</updated>
  <id>http://lukenpr.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Luke Martin]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why I decided to go analogue]]></title>
    <link href="http://lukenpr.com/2015/09/15/zombie-ninjas-attack-a-survivors-retrospective/"/>
    <updated>2015-09-15T17:30:51+10:00</updated>
    <id>http://lukenpr.com/2015/09/15/zombie-ninjas-attack-a-survivors-retrospective</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hi, I’m Luke, and I’m an organise-a-holic, and a little bit of a minimalist. I’m 21 years of age and tech savvy, even for millennial– the generation that lives and breathes in-app entertainment.</p>

<p>So, when I tell you that my experience with iPhone and Mac task managers was dismal, and that pen and paper was a better fit for managing myself, I’m not kidding!</p>

<p>Things.app set me back a whopping $64.99 AUD, which is a huge amount for any student, but I was willing to foot the bill for the extra structure in my life. I meticulously entered course details, lecturer contact information, and other details into Things.app on my Mac.</p>

<p>It took me hours to get the information that I wanted from my university’s Portal into the app, but I was satisfied when it was finished.</p>

<p>I fell in love with it at first sight! I then began to enter hundreds of tasks for different assignments, coffee times, and doctors’ appointments into their individual ‘Areas’ and ‘Projects’. Things.app is an organisers dream, but it came with one major problem–</p>

<p>I forgot that I was using it.</p>

<p>I simply forgot that I had entered tasks in the app! I was devastated, because I had paid so much money for an app that I couldn’t use, which wasn’t even because of shortcomings in the app, it was because of me!</p>

<p>Wunderlist.app
My girlfriend introduced me to Wunderlist, which I had heard about, but had never explored.</p>

<p>My experience was better with Wunderlist. I found the simpler interface much easier to use when I was in a hurry, plus the iPhone app felt like it worked better for me.</p>

<p>Perhaps I was a little biased, because my girlfriend and I were using it to plan our perfect date in Sydney (Mizuya!).</p>

<p>In the end, Wunderlist suffered the same fate as Things! I simply forgot that I had entered extremely important tasks into it, and therefore missed a lot of appointments. Bummer!</p>

<p>Notepad and pen (.app?)</p>

<p>It was another semester before I dared to try another system again. I walked into Officeworks and behold, a notebook that I just had to have! I bought myself a $14.95 (AUD) RHODIA UNLIMITED pocket notebook.</p>

<p>It took me a few hours to figure out what exactly I would use my new impulse by for, but it dawned upon me that I could use it to fill my task-manager void!</p>

<p>Fear of letting my illegible writing ruin
the beautiful paper crippled me.</p>

<p>My handwriting is quite flawed due to not actually practicing since I left school at the age of 17 (four years ago), so it took some bravery to actually write the first stroke, but in the end I figured out a system.</p>

<p>The left page is my task list, and the right page is my notes. For my task list, I put square boxes next to the task, and <code>X</code> cross them off when I’m done with them. The reason why I use an <code>X</code> and not a tick is because the tick often crosses out the bounds of the box, and annoys me.</p>

<p>Since I’ve had my notepad, I’ve completed much more than I would have with Wunderlist and Things.</p>

<p>Needless to say, paper won out, because it is difficult to forget something when you can physically feel it in your back pocket.</p>

<p>So, how do you do task management?</p>

<p>Send me a tweet: @ldmux</p>

<p>Happy task managing!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
